crestron.com 2018-08-12

# Privacy Policy [Crestron Electronics, Inc.]

### Crestron Respects Your Privacy

Crestron Electronics, Inc. (“Crestron”) respects your privacy and understands that the security of your personally identifying information (“PII”), provided to us through our Website, is important to you.

This Privacy Policy explains Crestron’s practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information received through our Website in the normal course of business. By accessing Crestron’s Website, located at https://www.crestron.com (the "Website"), and/or submitting information to Crestron through the Website, visitors consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy may be updated by Crestron from time to time, and your continued use of the Website, following the posting of such updated Privacy Policy terms, constitutes your consent to such updated Privacy Policy. The use of the Website is also governed by the Website Terms of Use, posted at http://www.crestron.com/legal/website-terms_of_use.

Information submitted through the Website is transmitted to servers at Crestron facilities and/or to cloud‐based storage, controlled by Crestron and/or trusted third parties, which are located in the United States of America (USA) and other countries

#### Personal Information Collected

Our server records the IP address of each visitor to our Website, along with details of your visits, such as the date, time, and length of each visit and the resources that you access. We may use this information to evaluate and improve our Website.

Crestron may collect PII you provide through your use of our Website including:  
• Website browsing;  
 Account registration;  
• Product ordering and registration;  
• Requests for information, support, service or assistance;  
• Registration for training, events, mailing lists or other materials;  
• Completion of Website forms or surveys; and  
• Other inquiries.

Crestron does not collect sensitive PII through the Website. The types of information collected by Crestron include:  
• Email address, phone number, address and other contact information;  
• IP address;  
• Your responses and feedback;  
• Account registration information;  
• Information about projects using Crestron products and services; and  
• Other information provided by you or by your authorized Crestron dealer or service provider (“Authorized Integrator”), when you or your Authorized Integrator visit this Website.

In addition to the information addressed in this Privacy Policy, certain Crestron products, including mobile apps, cloudware, and hardware devices; collect and transmit information directly to Crestron via the Internet, as described in the Crestron Privacy Statement Regarding Internet Data Collection, located at http://www.crestron.com/legal/crestron-privacy-statement-regarding-internet-data-collection, which may also be updated periodically.

#### How We Use Your Personal Information

In order to better manage our own business needs and to better communicate with you, we may collect, analyze and use your information for the following purposes:  
• To provide you with products, services, technical support and customer service  
• To process payments, orders, and returns  
• To personalize your Website experience  
• To inform you of new products or services  
• To offer you promotions, and other programs and opportunities  
• To invite you to events  
• To respond to inquiries, questions and other requests  
• To grant you access to our training and proprietary content  
• To provide pricing, quotations and custom configurations of our products  
• To improve our products, services, technical support and customer service  
• To manage our events and activities  
• To aggregate with other information and analyze  
• To use for our internal operations and processes

#### When We Disclose Your Personal Information

Crestron will only disclose the PII you submit for the purposes described in this policy. Crestron does not sell or rent your PII to other companies or marketers, and will share it only with certain trusted parties, as set forth in this policy.

Crestron is a global company, and we may transfer your information to Crestron subsidiaries, affiliates, representatives, or third parties contractors acting on our behalf worldwide. We also may transfer your contact information to certain partners that Crestron has a strategic relationship with or companies that provide products and services to you.

We may retain third parties to process, manage, analyze, safeguard or protect your information, fulfill orders, or deliver products and services. Use of your information by such third parties shall be limited to that described in this policy. We will ask your permission before we share your personal information with third parties for any purpose other than that described in this policy. We do not transfer your personal information to third parties unless those third parties agree to give the information the equivalent level of protection that we provide.

Crestron will disclose your personal information to a third party if required to do so by law or if, in good faith, Crestron believes that such action is necessary to comply with laws, statutes, or government rules and regulations.

#### Security of your Personal Information

Crestron is committed to protecting the security of your PII. We use a variety of security technologies and precautions, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol, to help protect your personal information from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, in accordance with industry standards. When using this Website, access to your Crestron account is password-protected, and secure https access to the Website is offered for pages used to create, update and log into your account. To protect any data stored on Crestron servers or cloud-based storage, we regularly monitor our systems for vulnerabilities or attacks.

Access to PII that is stored by Crestron is limited only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to process it on Crestron’s behalf, in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and that have agreed not to disclose it to others.

#### Use of Cookies

Crestron uses cookies to enhance your experience while visiting our Website. Cookie file(s), which are stored on the hard drive of your computer, enable us to obtain information about your usage of our Website, and to measure and improve the performance of our Website. Cookies enable you to store your preferences, in order to enable our Website to recognize these preferences when you browse our Website.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse cookies. However, if you select this setting you may not be able to access certain sections or features of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies to your computer whenever you log on to our Website.

#### Children’s Information

Creston’s Website is not intended for the use of anyone under the age of 18. In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we never collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of the Website is designed to attract anyone under 13.

#### Third Party Links

The Website contains links to other websites. Crestron is not responsible for the privacy policy of other websites, or the manner in which they store, use or distribute information. Crestron encourages you to review the privacy policy of any website you may visit.

#### Retention of Information, Correction, Opt-Out, and Other Inquiries

Crestron will retain your information as long as your account remains registered, or until the information is no longer necessary to provide products or services, or comply with legal, contractual and/or other obligations of Crestron. Crestron will, on its own initiative, or at your request, correct any inaccurate PII obtained by Crestron in connection with the Website.

If you decide you no longer want to receive certain marketing communications you may opt-out by selecting unsubscribe from any of our emails, or by email request to [support@crestron.com](mailto:support@crestron.com).

Crestron will address any inquiries regarding personal information promptly and courteously. For additional information or questions, please contact [support@crestron.com](mailto:support@crestron.com).

#### Contact Information

Address: Crestron Electronics, Inc. 15 Volvo Drive Rockleigh, NJ 07647  
Telephone: 201.767.3400  
e-mail: support@crestron.com

Last updated October 19, 2017
